

Abdul Ghanni

Software Developer



081293307289



abghanni@gmail.com



abdulghanni.github.io

ABOUT

i am a software developer with more than 5 years experience, I have been working for 2 Companies & Dozen Clients. My Speciality is developing Web & Application using PHP with some frameworks, i experienced to build desktop application using Java & Oracle Forms Developer, and now i'm a little bit



instagram.com/ghanni_abdul/



linkedin.com/in/abdulghanni/



github.com/abdulghanni

SKILLS

PHP (Native/Codeigniter/Laravel/YII2) Java (J2ee/Android) AngularJS/NodeJS MySQL/SQLServer/Oracle/PostgreSQL .Net Frameworks

LANGUAGES



English



Bahasa Indonesia

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

PT. Komunigrafik | 2014-2016

Contribute in planning and analyzing the system, take full responsibility in making the design and code of software programs, perform deployement, UAT and user training, system maintenance and improvement if needed

IT Software Development

PT. Cipta Mandiri Wirasakti | 2016-Now

As IT software development staff, i've responsibility developing new and existing system, maintenance databases,network and hardware.

EDUCATION

• Gunadarma University

Faculty of Computer Science & Information Technolgy, 2010-2014

Web Development With PHP & MySQL Course

University of Gunadarma, 2013

XML Intensive Workshop

University of Gunadarma, 2013

PORTFOLIO

HRIS PT.Penerbit Erlangga

Web Developer | October 2014 - June 2015

Analysis, UI Design, Coding, Deploy, UAT, User Training, Maintenance

Attendance & Payroll System PT. Mitsubishi

Web Developer | November 2015 - April 2016

Analysis, UI Design, Coding, Deploy, UAT, User Training, Maintenance

Cipta Manufacturing System

Software Developer

Build new system, Improve Existing System, User Training

Personnel System PT. CMW

Software Developer

Build new system, Improve Existing System, User Trainng

And Many More.....